This isn't getting us anywhere.
You can call me for Majo.
How do you like that?
Did it feel good?
I know he's waiting to
follow me back to the others.
Let him try.
And if he tries to get
in my way, he's dead!
This mission is in the bag!
Am I hearing things?
Or did a bomb go off?
What the hell was that?
We'd better retreat
for now, little bomber.
I know that Katsone's
hiding somewhere nearby,
but I gotta focus on getting out of here.
It's not gonna be pretty if I bring out my
stand with all these
people hanging around.
What the?
How'd my face stop bleeding?
I could have sworn he got me pretty deep.
Huh?
Where the hell did this come from?
It's too big to be mine.
This behemoth is practically a
machete.
Gotta focus.
Now where'd my knife go?
There's no way these
clown shoes could be mine.
They're freaking gigantic.
Come on, first my knife, now my shoes?
Wait a second.
There's There's something
strange about this seat.
And this steering wheel,
my arms don't reach.
I can't touch the pedal,
and the seat is crazy big.
I can't even see over the
dashboard in this damn thing.
This is some bullshit.
Where'd my freaking car go?
I was just sitting in it, so how in the
world did it up and vanish without a trace?
I'm totally stuck here
without those wheels, damn it.
You're a special kind of stupid, kid.
You're too dense to realize
your whole body is shrinking,
meaning my powers have kicked in.
Looks to me like that little
scratch I gave you did the trick.
Wait, what if these shoes
and this knife are mine?
That would mean I'm...
So it finally dawned on your dumb ass.
Your ship has sailed.
Good luck driving away from this
fight with that body, jailbait.
Well, at least now I know how
that stalker guy's powers work.
You are about to tell me where
the boss's daughter is hiding.
Let the pissing contest begin.
Hope you're ready to spill your guts, kid.
Thank you.
FIGHTING GOAL
Fighting God!
But these guys need the nourishment.
It's been too long, don't you think?
It's as I thought.
This just proves that he
shouldn't have been the one to go.
You still on about that?
Get over it.
I will not get over it!
I told you this was...
Sorry.
I didn't mean to snap at you.
Anything Tiny Feet slices
shrinks into oblivion.
I look mad,
it takes a little bit to get started,
but you can't argue with the results.
That get-up and bandana you're
sporting are shrinking along with you.
The dwindling dimensions of your shoe and
knife halted the moment
they left your body.
Put into dead man's terms, your entire
world is outgrowing you at an alarming rate.
Yeah, that's it!
I've gotta contact Bucciarati!
Ow!
What the heck is going on with this door?
Just great!
I'm still getting smaller!
That must be it!
I'm so light, the mechanism
that opens the door won't work!
Exactamente, you blockhead. Still! Huh?
If I want some help,
I've gotta get myself to that phone
before I shrink down to nothing!
Now here we go!
And that's the way you open a door!
Oh, come on!
Give me a break!
Talk about a waste of effort.
Guess it still hasn't dawned
on you that your wallet
and clothes have also been
shrinking along with you.
And you can't make a phone call
without a phone card or some coins!
Good luck phoning your friends
with that pint-sized pocket change!
So, he has some brains in there after all.
I'm gonna be in some deep shit if
his buddies find out how I operate.
And if Bucciarati gets wind of my powers,
he'll just hide the bitch somewhere else.
It'll be the ultimate disaster!
I have to act fast!
I have had enough!
I know you're around here somewhere!
Are you over here?
Or down here maybe?
Que Ball.
You've got two to three minutes
before you're the size of a cockroach.
Soon your stand will be as
tragically weak as it is small.
Then I'll really have
some fun torturing you.
I can already taste victory.
It's unfortunate, really.
He can't find me, but I
still need to wait. Dick!
You're hiding in my back pocket!
You sneaky bastard!
So your power is shrinking things down,
and you were hiding in my
pocket this whole time!
Freakin' A.
Figures that your powers would
match your puny personality.
What the hell's going on?
How'd he figure out I was in his pocket?
Lil' Bomber!
Massacre this runt!
Time to turn back!
What the ballpoint
pen you bastard where'd
you go and what the hell did you just do?
You listening quit the stalker
shit and fight me fair and square!
Shit that was close it takes a
lot of energy to do it so whenever
tiny feet has to shrink Anything
other than myself i need time on my
side returning things like that pen
to their original Size is another
story entirely the instantaneous
repulsion that created catapulted
me up and out Of his hands and
way over to here that said how did
the kid know i was there at all
guess it's Possible i could have
been moving around too much and
tipped him off
there's no way he
couldn't have Possibly seen me so
how the hell did he figure it out?
There you are.
You're not getting away stalker boy
Oh my god
Shit screw this party feet?
Whoa!
Where'd that asshole go? We're not done!
That was way too close for comfort.
If it hadn't been for that tire pressure,
I'd probably be a dead man right now.
At least he won't be able to find me, Don.
No freaking way.
Stan doesn't just blast shit to bits.
It has another ability.
Somehow it's finding my location
and tracking my every move.
There's no other way.
He has to be using something more
than just movement or sound detection.
Otherwise, how would he have known
that I was hiding out in his pocket?
Or that I used that blast of air?
Well, Leaky here, you
were hiding in the train!
Seriously?
They can still find me even
when I'm underwater like this?
Go, Tiny Feet!
Damn it!
Think, think, think, think, think!
This can't be happening!
Not like this!
The Hitman team has nine members.
Formaggio is counted among their numbers.
I'll be addressing waste
management at the meeting.
During Parliament? Yes.
I'll make the Minister of the
Environment choose the best option.
Just like always.
I just worry you may be working too hard.
Don't you think you've had
enough to drink this evening?
What the hell's with you, Pesci?
Are you really back to drinking milk?
Yeah, cut me some slack.
I don't want to drink it, but espresso
always makes my tummy all rumbly.
Really?
And you wonder why I refer
to you as Mamoni? You know,
you sipping on milk like
some lame-ass suckling
doesn't exactly do much
for our reputation.
Why do you think we even brought you
along with us in the first place?
Cut it out and get your shit together.
Yeah, will do.
So, Formaggio, how are things going?
There, Pesci.
Just consider it a gift.
From me to you.
Then things are moving smoothly.
You bet your ass.
The job's as good as done.
We can just sit back and enjoy the show.
Now let's get the hell out of
here and go watch some calcium.
That was excellent. Crazy.
We hope you will visit us again.
Right.
How about we finish this?
That was wonderful.
The Vino Bang was stupe - What's
going on? What's the matter?
Hey, you can't park your ass here!
Get out of the way!
Is that blood seeping
out from under the top?
Come on, time to bounce. Yeah.
What's the matter, Pesci?
Your leg's broken.
Honey, we're back!
How did it go?
Went perfectly, of course.
Rat bastard's nothing
but a bunch of smoke now.
But you offed the bitch
who was tagging along.
Don't forget. Hey, now.
Looks like your good-for-nothing
stance good for something, after all.
You keep talking.
You don't like how I work?
You do it.
Just between us.
How much was this job, Malone?
20 million lira.
Is that all it's worth?
Gyacho, take it easy.
We'll talk finances later.
We have more pressing matters.
Where are Sorbet and Gelato?
Do you think they're playing hooky?
Maybe they're making sweet, sweet love.
Crazy kids to be in love.
Man, do you ever shut your mouth?
I don't know.
There's something strange here.
Gelato is one thing, but Sorbet
definitely likes his money.
You can always count on that one to show
up in time to claim his cut of the pie.
There comes a time in the life
of every established organization
when the workers finally rise up
and rebel against the leaders.
And when smuggling drugs from
Central Asia to Europe and the U .S.
can be done cheaply,
profits can multiply by a hundred
times more than the original price.
Leading to the phenomenon of
the emboldened risk-taker,
who attempts to seize up drug lord's
territory even at the cost of their own life.
Did you find them?
No, there's no sign of them anywhere.
Then they must have been eliminated!
That's what they get for
trying to sniff out the boss!
It's possible.
They're both lunatics.
Polpo controls the gambling network.
Those goons handling the drugs
are making a killing too.
But us Hitman team losers are getting
nothing but chump change from the boss!
It's starting to get to me!
There ain't a single person
in the Family better than us!
We deserve way more respect around here!
So it was asphyxiation? That's right.
But only gelato's been ID'd.
We don't have Sorbet's body.
Punishment.
Several days later a shipment
of anonymous packages
mysteriously arrived
at the team's doorstep.
This is getting out of hand who's sending
these if I had a name
that'd be all she wrote.
Looks like a frame but this
isn't a painting so is this some
kind of modern art I see something
Weird floating in them what
look inside the frame that's the
same color nail Polish sorbet
always wears I've seen it before
he and gelato use the same shade
Get the frames off and line them up.
36 works of art had arrived
at the team's hideout.
This can't be real. It's
a joke! It's gotta be!
I can't look anymore!
Quit your crying!
This is
the slabs held sorbet's
preserved sliced body
the slices formed a face
contorted in terror the face of a
man who was tortured with a
razor-sharp blade from head to toe?
It was a way of sharpening
and prolonging the pain,
and for the Hitman team,
it was a day of revelation.
Hey guys, you don't think Sorbet was
sliced up right in front of Gelato, do you?
Yeah, the fear and anguish
must have made him.
Well, let's just say he probably
used the gag to suffocate himself!
Without speaking a word, the
boss had made his message clear.
Listen, from this moment on,
the two of them never existed.
The team knew and accepted
that they were on thin ice.
Uncovering the boss's true identity
was unequivocally off the table.
That is, until news of the boss's
daughter reached their ears.
Like hell, I'm gonna die
here like a common rat!
Boss and his sweet drug business are
ours, and no one's taking it away!
We're not just giving up!
We're gonna claw our way up to the top!
It's riddled with holes?
But why would he shoot that rat to death?
Could it be?
It went the other way.
It's trying to weed me out.
Respiration! That's it!
Narancia's stand detects and
follows its victim's respiration.
It's the exact same way mosquitoes
feed on the blood of their victims,
by detecting the carbon dioxide
they give off when they breathe.
That has to be it.
It's how he found me in his pocket, too.
And that must have been why he gave
up the hunt back in the alleyway.
When all those onlookers started
crawling out of the woodwork,
he could have hit an innocent bystander.
It was tracking my
breathing from the start.
There you are.
He shot again.
It looks like he can't tell the difference
between me and the rats down here.
In that case...
Look at these disgusting
excuses for mammals.
There are so many of them.
And their movements.
I must be tracking a pack of rats.
They're going the same speed.
And they're moving the same way.
You're good, kid.
But now I know how your powers work.
I didn't know how you were finding me.
Now that I do, you're about as worrisome
as a pesky mosquito on a balmy suit.
It's a summer night, Narancia!
I win, Narancia!
I'm getting out of here
and waiting for you
to shrink into oblivion where you belong!
Huh?
How could he have...
Every rat in the pack
moves the exact same way.
But there was one rat that was huffing and
puffing a lot more than any of the others.
Are you tired?
Out of breath, maybe?
Could a traveler be hitching
a ride on your back?
I'm feeling lucky.
And getting a little target practice in
might do me a world of good! Not good!
Direct hit!
That was too close.
If I hadn't returned to my normal
size, I'd be dead right now.
Luckily, time was on my side.
Your wimp-ass shrinking down to nothing
again was the best thing
to ever happen to me! Damn!
He's still breathing!
My Stan's power!
Could this bastard's ability have
made it shrink along with my size?
How the hell am I supposed
to shoot him dead now?!
You out of my mind?
Since you'll be all I see!
I would give anything.
Just to make you understand me!
I don't give a damn about nothing else!
Freaking you is all I need!
I need your brain!
Tonight you got my time!
Tonight you
won't be sorry!
Tonight you got my mind!
You got my mind!
All I wanna do is to free you!
What must I say?
What must I do?
To show how much I'm gonna freak you?
What must I say?
What must I do?
To show how much
I'm gonna freak you?
Thank you.